<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Typhon Wiki</title><link>https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Typhon Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Forums</title><link>https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/docs/community/forums/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 22:18:20 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/docs/community/forums/</guid><description>Forums # Dreadbox maintains a Facebook page with new announcements and some occasional Q&amp;amp;A. This Elektronauts thread has several owners and has been a good place to track the first few months of people experiences. A lot of info on this site was lifted from this thread.</description></item><item><title>Midi Cc</title><link>https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/docs/midi/midi-cc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 22:16:55 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/docs/midi/midi-cc/</guid><description>MIDI CC List # This is the list of MIDI CC, as of firmware v2.0.2. All are CC, so far there aren&amp;rsquo;t any NRPN.
CC# Function Notes 0 BANK SELECT Added in 2.0.2. Set this CC first to pick the bank (1=A, 2=B, 3=C, 4=D), then send a MIDI program change to select a preset 1 MOD WHEEL 2 CC2 Assignable in CC2 Target Menu: CV.</description></item><item><title>MIDI mods</title><link>https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/docs/projects/midi-mods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/docs/projects/midi-mods/</guid><description>MIDI mods # MIDI start/stop filter # The Midiboy is an Arduino-compatible board for MIDI prototyping. This sketch is a hack of the MIDI monitor that will block the MIDI start/stop/continue messages. MIDI clock events still pass through. This will let you sync the modulators to the BPM of other MIDI devices, but skip the Typhon&amp;rsquo;s internal sequencer. This is great if you want to use an external sequencer but still keep your effects synced to the beat.</description></item><item><title>Tutorial Videos</title><link>https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/docs/community/videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadboxunofficial.github.io/TyphonWiki/docs/community/videos/</guid><description>Tutorial Videos # Loopop has posted a very good walkthrough of the Typhon explaining how the oscillator &amp;amp; filter adjustments work, how to use the modulators and FX, as well as some example patch ideas. The step mod section is especially helpful and includes a chart going from the 0-100 range to semitones. This video used the v1.1 firmware, so some of the newer FX are not covered.</description></item></channel></rss>